foreign
[Music]
I'm here
with Amanda seals and she just taught me
how to say Quasar not quasi Give It Up
this is huge I'm super excited I told
um I want to be as black as I can I told
this [ __ ] when she came in here I
thought that she was six foot I don't
know if y'all know that about me
um I am extremely impressed with like
intelligence and like school and stuff
like that my mother the family that I'm
raised in is all female everybody has
some kind of education behind them
um only my eyes are chemist like how
many black women chemists do we need she
she worked for the duponts for years
shout out to Bernice Grimes
um my aunt has a bachelor degree in
Psychology she has her own practice my
mother's been a LPN for a thousand years
but my mother is the smartest person I
know in the world y'all remember
and what look at that everything's in
comment and you know that that that that
job is such a hard trying job doubles
and triples but it can't afford you a
certain kind of Lifestyle
um did weekends at nursing homes and
double my mother did bariatric
geriatrics too did you ever talk to
people like in a dementia unit for fun I
I did not I did not
well my mom would say I will be calling
my mother and harassing her work Mommy
can I get some chips mommy can you order
pizza Mommy and she will go hold on Tom
this is this is her this is Brenda and
he would go Brenda I've been waiting on
you by the lake yes and I would talk oh
[ __ ] god with dementia for 20 minutes
cause my mother's hilarious but no
um I was telling a man that I
yeah
you the way that I learned the way I
take things at I've never been
necessarily like a reader I have added
such deficit disorder it's very you
probably do I um it's very hard for me
to like lock into things I have been in
love with documentaries since I was
about 14. and I learned a lot from them
um but then we got this special thing
called Instagram you know social media
and
um depending on who you follow or where
you are you can get some real pertinent
information you know you are one that
always gave it to me like I needed it if
you got
um just super intelligent super Brave
you know
um I always and then I feel like you do
a good job of putting things in the
simpler terms right so of course you got
your big words you got whatever whatever
but you can kind of talk to the you know
the people in a way that and I get that
compliment myself although you know we
all have our own insecurities and things
like that when I think about when I
speak speak the way I want to speak you
or who I think about I told you earlier
like I would wish I would be like at a
press conference I'm sitting there and
then you like get up at me and I turn
into you for a second
then it go away and I'm like yeah [ __ ]
blah blah blah blah but I just want to
compliment you on your big brain you
know you're smart you're smart that
means a lot yeah it's hard being smart
in 2022
yeah because
I think
um we are in the I not I think I know
that we are in what I call the age of
idiocy
and uh there's just a lot of people who
are talking out their neck
um unfettered you know just just
right and feeling very empowered to do
so because other people with more power
are doing the same thing like when we
had a president that was really just out
here acting an ass like funky time
everybody's like well [ __ ] I can act an
ass too and then maybe I'll become
president right so I think that's really
kind of the thing and I just
we we're also seeing the result of less
like critical thinking not really being
like touted as important we're seeing
the result of like our education system
not really showing up for teachers and
so teachers aren't able to show up the
way they want to for their students so
like we're just we see the result of
that when we look on the internet
um but I will say that I have hope
because I really thought after this
election like I genuinely was like we
we're about to descend into a new level
of darkness and
I just was so relieved to see that it
wasn't it's not amazing but it wasn't as
bad as I thought it was and America
wasn't as heartless it's this this place
is still not
we still don't Center education the way
we should but it wasn't as heartless as
I thought it was which is really what
people are voting for when they vote for
you know
these folks that say very clearly that
we don't care about women we don't care
about black people we don't care about
immigrants we don't care about you and
your kids we don't care about any of
these things we care about corporations
and our money you know so to answer your
question yes I think it's hard for
anybody who is smart in an environment
where that is not considered to be like
a positive thing and I've been in the
environments I've been in both you know
I mean it's not like I think sometimes
it sucks when people try and make it
like you're elitist if you're smart and
it's like anybody's trying to be elitist
I'm just not trying to have dumb
conversations I don't like small talk I
hate chit chat I want to start a medium
talk yeah yeah I for me I mean because
I'm a real [ __ ] I'm right open it's
intimidating it can be intimidating
especially in but it's all about what
you think of yourself yeah I have an
insecurity about how I speak right and
it's because and I think people don't
understand it's like when millions of
people are hanging on your every word or
criticizing it right sometimes you'll
pick that up you know but with me prior
to that I remember being a kid and
everybody would be talking and I would
say excuse me I was well and I was and I
remember I turned around and said you
gotta just jump in because they will be
talking about every in the conversations
were always about
um like politics and climate change and
this and that it was it was always some
deep [ __ ] but I always had something to
say and I remember being able to do that
and hang on and I could make a point and
then a funny I'm like oh [ __ ] this is
it I'm in but now at this point I shared
with Amanda earlier about what my mother
said is that I had to do my dude
diligence is I have a response of
[ __ ] ability to know what I'm talking
about it's a total different thing when
you got all these [ __ ] like
hanging on you every word in some kind
of way I've been amassed this like these
young girls yeah and that [ __ ] is like
you [ __ ] listen to me like they asked
me for advice and they take it
open with like I don't know what I'm
doing but what I represent for a lot of
people and I think you do too is like
their freedom to say what you want to
say you know in like the balls like to
like stand on it to mean it but you know
what let me just rain that in because I
feel like there's a lot of conversation
I'm seeing about like freedom of speech
oh God and it's really just people
thinking that you can say what you want
and that there shouldn't be any
consequences for saying what you want
bro and I had said on my Instagram like
anybody who think that ain't been
punched in the face before because that
at the end of the day you know there's a
saying that says uh Lessons Learned
lessons not learned in blood are easily
forgotten you can't just say whatever
you want what was the other one [ __ ]
around and find out [ __ ] around and find
out you can't just say what you want and
you also need to know that if you gonna
say you better be able to stand hand on
it Amanda yes ma'am these [ __ ] will
walk down on you and ask you about what
you said when you're in a public forum
you could be at Target what you gonna do
when the [ __ ] come and ask you what you
gonna do and that's what I'm saying The
Bravery I said what I said and I meant
that and this is why and I don't think
people understand what comes with that
because people don't always like what
the [ __ ] you say no and people will Buck
at you people will no I got into the
hugest I know y'all might be a bit tired
of hearing about it debate on social
media because somebody I follow who is
of Latin descent said I wish you guys
value your lives a little more shut the
[ __ ] up
show over wrap it up thanks for joining
us don't call me white girl show I wish
they valued their lives a bit [ __ ]
more because you know how many Latinos
are out here like go Trump go Trump who
like want this [ __ ] dictatorship you
know how many Latinos don't give a [ __ ]
about black people because they want to
be white so bad that they have assigned
themselves to that whiteness it's gonna
be a [ __ ] conversation about I wish
you cared about your life so bad so much
how many are they also talking about the
migrants who are trying to come across
this border and are putting their lives
at stake in their children's lives at
stake are they talking about them
because they care about their lives but
they also know that this is what it is
and for black people we know what it is
I don't like that
was that
well I can't really discuss it and the
thing about it is is that this person is
in the beauty industry and
I would say out of 100 clients 99 of
them are black
because when she says something like
that that's othering don't know listen
on a public on the main page
um do you do you see what the Keith
Stanfield said I try not to oh right he
says something it was regarding
takeoff's death and it was summed up to
Hip Hop is trash turn it off takeoff is
dead because of rap [ __ ] we need to
stop listening to rap that's the root of
our problems it's the rap music and um
we need to Value ourselves something
like that she copied it pasted it repost
it and made the caption I wish you
[ __ ] loved yourself a bit more well
look Heath is an incredible actor
that's it so
um I listen at this point I've decided
I'm not going to waste my time in some
of these conversations because
[ __ ] don't really want to learn
they don't want to find out people had
the freedom of
um speech [ __ ] twisted and they don't
understand it that [ __ ] goes a whole
hell of a lot way when I responded to
this girl and I literally I didn't say
like [ __ ] I whip your ass it was simple
as hey you can't say that it's not yeah
you had a line you can't say that and
this is a horrible time to say that and
let me tell you why you can't say that
okay and her response was I [ __ ] three
[ __ ] last year my nephews are [ __ ] I
listen to [ __ ] all day long I got all
the dark-skinned people foundation and
that's why I can say it
and it was horrible and then so what
about like what about like the MS-13
and then and then the hypocrisy is
astounding why are you attacking me of
course you sending your followers to
attack me this is violent damona people
know me people and you know somebody
walks up to me and punches me because
you're pushing this narrative because I
pass for white and you think I'm white
and you should understand because you
passed for white you of all people
should know what it feels like to pass
for white [ __ ] what what the [ __ ] is
white passing what is that I passed for
white it's 2022 also you [ __ ] like
that I've had enough like that I've
decided that I'm not going to engage in
conversations with stupid people if I
feel on the other end that you don't
want to learn anything about this
conversation relieve yourself we done
baby because I have listen I'm still
trying to get my son to wipe his ass
good okay he's still streaking the draws
baby okay she ain't wearing ethicals
they twenty dollars a piece yeah you
can't do doing them now you're trying to
embarrass them but he gonna wipe his ass
good and he probably gives you some
other things to focus on what's the more
important things I don't want your niece
to be [ __ ] girl look at his [ __ ]
draws and that's my son yeah I [ __ ]
don't call me right girl son he has
streaks in his drawers how dare I be a
part of that so I'm teaching my kid how
to maybe wet the tissue before he wipes
his ass wipes dry it okay Muslims call
it Stinger the practice of spraying your
ass with water okay and wiping age right
that's where I'm at I'm not trying to
educate some 33 year old woman I'm not
trying to teach women you're not trying
to teach her how to wipe her ass because
she's full of [ __ ]
if you saw
you saw this girl's ass
let's stop it let's be mature as much as
we can but and I'll and I encourage you
all to do that at home because I did
share it and my followers were going
crazy writing paragraphs and [ __ ] like
that but it's like it's draining yeah
but that's the thing about this whole
freedom of speech thing right
she had the full freedom to say what she
wanted to say and those people also have
the full freedom to respond yeah and so
that's why there's a thoughtfulness that
you have to have about what you say and
you better be able to stand on it when
people come for me I don't engage with
them nine times out of ten just because
I'm like I know what I said like I
didn't say the [ __ ] flippantly I didn't
say this [ __ ] thoughtlessly you trying
to come and change my mind or whatever
whatever you wasting your time because
I'm not somebody who's out here saying
[ __ ] just to say [ __ ] but there are a
lot of people who yes and I think that
that was a part of because another thing
that I because it's just some things
that I see on the internet a lot and it
bothers me so much even some of my peers
there's people that I've worked with and
I watch them write stuff like
um this is why we need Trump and it's
like yo not only do I not want to work
with you anymore [ __ ] I don't even want
to speak to you anymore now there is
this really huge misconception in the
ghetto a lot of people feel because
there were some may say free money out
they attribute that to Donald Trump the
thing about it is we're Americans
television raises us and our children
you know and Donald Trump is a TV star
and he's also
um some might call him charismatic or
you know I don't know Donald Trump
reminds me of like you ever see like a
turd on the ground and there's something
in it so I'll catch your eye cause you
think is that corn that's what I would
say about what Donald Trump does for me
I know who Donald Trump is I know who he
was when he got in office I was never
like impressed by him I never really I
did laugh at the China I did that was it
that was the one I liked the little
China that one but other than that I
didn't really like enjoy any of it you
know what I mean
um I remember coming to Jersey and
wiping out those small businesses and
making those people who file bankruptcy
when you know when he blew all that
smoke up in people's asses white people
you know [ __ ] their financial
um situations up with um you know coming
in and not finishing what he had to do
with the casinos and [ __ ] I know that
about Donald Trump I've remembered the
Central Park five minutes letter that he
wrote and put in the newspaper right and
so it's like it and I remember watching
documentary about him calling a
journalist saying hey I represent Donald
Trump in the general saying is this you
Donald and him hanging up he's a loser
right he's a loser that comes from a
family with a couple of dollars you know
what I mean you know who likes him
losers
oh like we know like you know it just
went because it's like like I see myself
in you you know what I mean like I think
that's really what it is because they
see that he got over and they like that
means I can get over too bro and how
many losers have we met but he got over
with a with a very very rich daddy you
Jerome are not getting over that way I
don't give a [ __ ] which is social
security check looks like from your
father you know it's like at the end of
the day it bothers me that people people
think about him and they think money or
they think like abundance he literally
is a terrible business person the worst
ever it's like if he had a trap that
trap would have to close what are you
[ __ ] selling the money like really you
have to shut down the Trap like any time
and time again business Mentor at their
business venture at their business
and it's like the fact that some of my
peers say [ __ ] like that it's just like
what the [ __ ] and after you say [ __ ]
like that line you can't come back to
the show we can't text we can't talk
it's that serious it is because I love
that it's that serious for you I don't
think it's serious enough for people
listen that [ __ ] got he put a
certain energy in the air I always say
he made that you know that's scary white
[ __ ] they catch you in traffic
and goes [ __ ] and pulls off and
sometimes they get cold at the light and
they stuck and they say [ __ ]
everybody like us they don't know if
you're gonna jump out yourself to jump
out yeah jump out right
that's what he brung out he gave those
[ __ ] hard and that's some
dangerous when I saw Confederate flags
flying in the Bronx yo I was like oh
yeah okay pero you know
the good thing is that there's [ __ ]
like us ah and we have platforms
because and and I feel like you know
it's going to be a time where I don't
know if I should say this but it's like
God might have to come delete podcasts
it's too many it's too many of us here
everybody has the setup and these [ __ ]
are just well that Dookie out their
mouth just constantly you know what
though I follow a page on Instagram
called the Tennessee holla and like they
do a lot of political stuff that's
happening like just in Tennessee but
also just in general but regardless
their their their bio says yell the
truth and I just love that small little
statement because
that's really what it has to be at this
point we have to yell the truth I think
for a lot of us there was a very big
energy of like oh they dumb over there
talking yeah you know and so then let me
preserve my energy and not even engage
right like you said earlier there is a
certain level of self-preservation that
you have to have about engaging with
folks that are just committed to not
knowing and yeah but when you're in your
space it has to be like a very committed
intention
to just being loud about not going along
with the [ __ ] [ __ ] you know like when I
do stand up I'm on stage and I'm talking
about you know the difference between
hood [ __ ] and [ __ ] in front and
[ __ ] from the hood you know I'm
talking about relationships but I'm also
making time to talk about Roe v Wade and
talk about gun control and talk about
this this fish looking [ __ ] Clarence
Thomas and like it's because I feel like
it's the responsibility that I have to
do that because we got to yell the truth
because these folks are so loud with the
misinformation that we gotta like
challenge them Yo it
okay because I don't want to go too far
okay I was gonna say I feel like I don't
want this to be a whole interview about
politics because I want to have fun baby
the black on black crime thing yeah I
can't sleep okay I'm losing sleep about
it
um and the reason why I'm losing sleep
about it because the number one person
that bought that [ __ ] is my people I I
did a black lives matter rally because
I'm an activist Mona X I don't know if
you heard of me
um my grandmother told me I was gonna be
active when I was like nine years old to
stand in front of a sea of people and do
the first the first of its kind in the
city of Wilmington Delaware was huge for
me right and I've never felt like that
before it's something that I want to do
but I understand how hard it is I just
watched the interview with I think her
name is Tamika Mallory Mallory and I
mean for the love of God I pushed her to
addiction like she had a rough ride with
that
um and I and it is so much pressure I
remember getting my daughter ready and
making her poster and then having like
about 10 different messages from the
mayor's office saying the mayor is
telling her State Police to shoot y'all
to kill y'all please don't take your
baby there morning let's not say maybe
you shouldn't go like it's a different
kind of
um thing when you you know it's just
it's a whole different Beast I came here
to be funny and have fun but I cannot I
can't sleep it's it it bothers me that
more than anything my people believe
that I did that Riley right and when the
crowd left and everybody hugged me and
just did so many wonderful things I had
an older woman that knew me since I was
a kid and she stood by my car and she
said I can't [ __ ] believe you just
lied to them people like that black on
black crime does exist these
Knuckleheads and I lost my grandson and
it's like but cut it cut it cut it cut
it cut it cut it cut it cut it cut it
cut it
when they say black on black crime
they say it
within the connotation that there isn't
also Asian on Asian crime that there
isn't also white on white crime there is
proximity crime
right like that's simply the facts you
are going to be more likely to get into
it with the people you live next to than
you are with the people in the
neighborhood over there right now if you
have a nation that has systematically
confined black folks to certain areas
through segregation has also
systematically limited black folks from
being able to ascend by prop with
property ownership with education access
with uh job Freedom with
disenfranchisement due to an
overwhelmingly
um skewed justice system then how are
you not going to have black people
harming other black people it is by
Design
so when we talk about the reality of
black on black crime we cannot do so in
a bubble in a vacuum that doesn't
include the Myriad of ways this country
has made efforts to ensure that black
people harm each other and then on top
of it when we don't do it to ourselves
they make sure they're right there to do
it to us so miss me with the concept of
quote unquote black on black crime as
some sort of
um
miss me with the term black on black
crime being used to describe black
people harming black people because we
are less caring about our lives or
because we are more Savage
etc etc that's completely uh uh myopic
and like real reductive way of looking
at [ __ ] I almost feel like that I am on
a campaign
to to just tell people about it I don't
think
I'm very in tune with my with my fans
with my people and
I mean some of them just they just
didn't know so it's like how often how
long and how loud are we going to have
to yell that part because that's
something for the rest of our lives
that's what you need to know
yeah
baby you're going to be well hopefully
you won't have to clean up shitty draws
so you know that's why I said my name to
[ __ ] it call me white girl because it's
a lot of struggle for love of God people
you know what I mean I could just go to
them Davis it's still like at protest
it's still like it doesn't stop until
it's it like it doesn't stop because the
culture and the value system hasn't
changed we had a place that ain't never
said slavery we shouldn't have done that
like
culturally we ain't never said that
there's been individuals who have been
like that was [ __ ] up but like America
as a society has never said we are doing
black people dirty we did black people
dirty and we need to like switch the
game up never why
why if if if if everyone knows right
that for the most part a majority of the
people that were wronged in some kind of
way they got some kind of reparation
right and Bennett it was written and we
were supposed to get our 40 acres
everyone then essentially kind of
written out and we didn't get it also
being that we're still like way behind
and [ __ ] is still [ __ ] up right
why are we going to get it I mean why
are we you said why are we going to get
it or why no
when are we going to get it because I
can't get another PP loan I'm going to
get in trouble you know what I mean I
took it I've taken We're not gonna get
it until we
um
until we get it
I think there's a lot of folks that
think access to whiteness
and access to um
money is the
let me take that back I think there's a
lot of folks I think individual access
to money
individual access to like white spaces
they consider that to be
like an advancement they consider that
to be progress what yeah and you know
that's the difference that's the value
system when we talk about when we talk
about the black community you know we're
not we're not a black community at this
point in the way that I think we once
were we're very very splintered in terms
of like what we see us deserving and
what we see as oppressive right I think
at one point in time and I may be
romanticizing this but at one point in
time I think there was a very much more
cohesive view of black people around the
nation saying like this [ __ ] is [ __ ]
up this [ __ ] is [ __ ] up and this [ __ ]
is [ __ ] up and we should all like be
against that and I don't think that
that's the case at this present time I
think a lot of people
got money and they like what's the
problem
you know like and I think I think a lot
of people
um
you know really believe the hype about
just like white [ __ ] but what I
really want to see though is just more
willingness for us to listen to each
other
and I when I do my show smart funny and
black you know I say in the show like
this is a community when I do my radio
show the Amanda seal show I end every
episode saying we are each other's
business when we look out for each other
we lift each other up because I think
that's something that we
have been really really a subject of and
I wouldn't lie I think these bots on
this internet be doing a really
effective job too of like dividing and
conquering and I just want to see
us as a unit come to get on the same
page about things in a in a more
effective way and that's where that that
I think that because we not get these
people came
over here for a couple reasons right you
had a group of the the Puritans came
over because they was on some wild [ __ ]
and even the white people over there was
like we ain't [ __ ] with you yeah
so they came over here on that and they
was talking about they're so Christian
but yet they over here and you know got
rid of all of these natives right the
Native American people that were here
already then you had the people who
literally just came over here like
what's going on over here oh this is
ours now these are not like these are
not the descendants of like
like valued you know ethical people so
the same way that we have like trauma
PTSD in our DNA they got shitty [ __ ]
value non-ethics in their DNA never
thought about it like that they didn't
come over here on some like let's
increase the Bountiful nature of this
place like no then they like because
white people don't really have a culture
oppression
wow that's the culture of whiteness
demonic that's the culture of whiteness
oppression whiteness was not created for
any other reason than to oppress there's
cultures within whiteness there is I
feel like if I was white I would be
like I would mean [ __ ] you
if I was a white woman there would be
nothing in me that felt for anybody who
had any empathy in fact it would slide
through my head my grandmother probably
owned yours
let me tell you something but that being
said though
when you do find these white women who
are co-conspirators because there's
levels of whiteness uh-huh when you find
a white woman who are co-conspirators
there is nothing a white woman on a
mission cannot get done what and if
there were enough white woman
co-conspirators this whole country would
turn around but there's just too many of
them that are still voting you know to
make their white men in power yeah yeah
yeah I
you know I ain't gonna I ain't gonna
beat you up beat you in the head with it
but I I do feel like okay it just it
just makes you want to like slam my face
into the wall sometimes it bothers me it
did because I feel like it's so in in
the person that bought it the most are
my people and it hurts my feelings a bit
when the Elon Musk thing happened with
Twitter and it was like the first thing
was like oh great you [ __ ] I finally
get to tell you how I kill you [ __ ]
[ __ ] right
it's like we're still here in 2022 I
dated a gamer you know guys that play
video games and when you play video
games that would you say that's a part
of it when people lose they get upset
they say wow you [ __ ] [ __ ] why
didn't you get the AK and do the hit
right we're on Grand Theft Auto but I'm
a dumb [ __ ] because I didn't get the
right prostitute and bounce the car race
whatever the [ __ ] y'all do on 2K or
whatever you do but that's but that's a
part of it and we're here in 2022 still
being hated for just being existing
um I don't know and it's like
it is beyond frustrating but I but I can
kind of like I could deal with it from
them like it's like I expect that of
them I don't expect it to you Shaquita
and the fact that we're debating in my
DM about about black on black right but
then you there's like a certain level of
Grace that you try to give sometimes
sometimes I you know I try my best to
give the grace of like well you know the
brainwashing it was effective and it
caused people got caught up yo you From
The Trenches and you've been watching
[ __ ] die your whole life and that's
all you know that's all you see I can
understand yes I can sympathize with you
but still I need you to know you don't
know enough black people to be thinking
that way because I think there's also
like
in that context like you need an
explanation because it's like why the
[ __ ] are so many of us dying right so
it's like like
as humans we like require we require
some type of explanation that's what
religion is we need some type of order
to make [ __ ] make sense right you know
because without it it feels like you're
just at the behest of whatever the [ __ ]
and so I think for a lot of people that
right there makes it make sense like
okay all of my peers are getting caught
up because black on black crime okay now
I've got something to sink my teeth into
and it's and it's um
but it's a misnomer you know and it's
unfortunate and then you get us and we
sit up here particularly I feel like
then I set up here and I say I talk my
[ __ ] and then it becomes like well you
just talking over you know you're not in
the trenches you're not there so who the
[ __ ] is you to run your [ __ ] mouth
and I'm like hey
[Music]
I'm from La Ghetto I'm burying friends
still black on black crime isn't real
it's a lie it is though it's a lie all
the time application
and the person that bought it the most
is your black ass right now getting
irritated that we're having this
conversation because you bought it and
it's like some white Force that's like
we got him again
it is true though yeah definitely
they're they're playing a whole
different video game yo this [ __ ]
they're like look at you dumb [ __ ]
you should have made the cow bounce you
should have made the car balance yikes
all right whatever I met you on MTV
that's where I found you
um
Yeah well yeah so being that you've been
in more than one industry how do you
feel about the music industry or
entertainment industry on that side
versus where you are now
Mona coming with the questions
um you know it's funny so I just started
this radio show
uh shout out to 100.3 wrnb and you are
here yes we are here in Philadelphia as
our first station can I come on yeah I
would love to have you oh my gosh I
would love to have you and if you don't
and if you don't live in Philadelphia
you can hear the radio show every day on
podcasts so it's the Amanda seal show
wherever you get your podcast okay
um
but I came back to radio I started I
started in radio back when I was leaving
college so it was my first job out of
college but I've been in TV for
a really long time I've been sagged
since Nickelodeon yes so I've been TV
since I was eight in TV since I was
eight and then I went in the music
business when I got out when I was in
school and when I got out of school how
does that happen though as an
eight-year-old was that your mother yeah
because we literally I was in Orlando
and my mom one morning like
was like she saw a an audition for a
Disney show in the newspaper and was
like oh let's go to this audition and I
remember saying you just want me to go
for you I don't even know where the [ __ ]
I got that from Wow and she was like
yeah he does get dressed and let's go
and so we went and I it was like 1500
kids and I got it and it was like Must
Be Santa Must Be Santa you know and you
had to do a little choreography but you
know what shout out to my mom because
she never said she never made that [ __ ]
like the Center of My Universe it was
just a part of the orbit like even that
there was a callback in the end of the
day so like we went in the morning and
then they were like okay you made it to
the next round you got to go to the
Callback I think most parents would be
like all right we're gonna go like sit
in the parking lot or you know we're
gonna go home and practice the steps we
went to like my mom's friend's house who
had a pool and let me swim in the pool
you know what I mean like it was like
okay let's carry on with the Sunday that
we had originally planned and then I
went back and I ended up getting it and
that was like the story of like how I
always dealt with the the entertainment
business it's never been the Center of
My Universe it's always been a thing I
do but not a thing I'm of right
[Music]
um and so when I got in the music
business
I'm I'm A hip-hop head me too like to
the core I think a lot of people at this
point in my career don't really know
that about me
um well tell them Amanda
I mean what you want to do like do we
want to do do I need to wrap the entire
mob deep the infamous album like do I
need to do it but if you want to
Freestyle
I used to be nice I do I always have two
verses in my back pocket I will say I
mean um did you not see me at the BET
Cypher that was me I spit in bars I
didn't [ __ ] around drove a car imma stop
there no it's crazy because when you are
a real hip-hop head right and you come
from where we come from in that in the
age of we saw when rap came out and it's
like what is this what is that thing too
oh my God what is this what is that
thing to Global takeover this is it we
run the world so I saw that when I was
in Lee like I entered the music business
at that time like late uh sorry early
2000s is when [ __ ] yeah really took over
right that's when like hard knock life
went like diamonds and Eminem
and so that was a really like wild like
dope time to be a part of that and like
when I was on MTV I'm interviewing hoes
and Nas and hello everybody that I like
looked up to DMX many times
I interviewed DMX many times what's his
funeral Cry of course he was crushed by
that
um when I graduated from Colombia I got
my Master's at Columbia and the day I
came to work and they had gotten me a
cake and I had to interview X that day
and the cake was in the studio and he
came in the studio and was like what up
uh and I was like hello Mr X and then he
saw the cake and um even though the cake
did say congratulations Amanda
um but he thought the cake was for him
and so he put his hand in the cake and
eat it and I was like that was my cake
and he was like congratulations
um and I was like all right but then now
I have that story yeah but you know X
all these folks like
for me like getting to be in that space
was like low-key like spiritual like it
was real and then at a certain time it
just stopped feeling like that um and I
knew that it was time to go yeah and so
that's when I pivoted and started like
looking for the next PATH and that's
when I found myself in comedy did you
lose any love for hip-hop with that one
thousand percent you know what it was
because the business started making me
hate the music because once I started
doing my own music and like trying to
navigate that space and having people
tell me like well you can't rap and sing
who does that you know which by the way
hilarious man
and and just like the idea that like
Talent didn't matter was like Wow to me
yeah like as a woman it was just like
that's irrelevant like what's your story
what are you willing to you know give to
this and I felt like in order for me to
be successful in music the way that at
the level I consider to be success I
would have had to give up more of me
than I was willing to um and so then you
know kind of just like
I'm a really big believer like I I re I
uh I receive Omens
you know people say [ __ ] to me and I
hear it you know I filter it through I'm
not a stubborn person by any means and I
knew that it was time to come back to TV
because there was just a lot of people
just kind of that that just kept getting
sprinkled into my aura and I knew that I
wanted to do that
even though I was hosting and stuff I
just knew there was more for me but I'll
say all this to answer your question
TV then became at this point in my life
TV has become a space
that doesn't feel like a creative outlet
for me
it doesn't feel
it doesn't feel like a place where I can
be my full self and so that doesn't make
it doesn't feel valuable to me that's
why I like getting to do this radio show
like I get to be my full authentic self
you're doing this podcast you get to be
your full authentic self and I had to I
had to come to the realization that I
was kind of chasing these these like
benchmarks in TV that were for other
people and that were for [ __ ] that that
were for other people who don't care
about being there like like that's not
how do I say it some people don't even
have it they don't have it they just
it's not what they that's not their
their reason for doing this [ __ ] you
know what I mean like and so
um you know TV will find
its way like there's like I want to do a
game show like that's really what I want
right now I would love to do a game when
you talk about smart and funny that's
what it sounds like what's my funniest
smart funny and black is a game show I
don't know that I would ever want to do
smart funny and black on TV until the
deal is that y'all give me a check and
then I give you a show right because
it's so stupid
it's yours and it's too black I love it
and I can't put that in other people's
hands and I've I've tried to [ __ ] it up
well they've already tried I mean I sold
it to this network True TV and they were
like so we'd love to have Michael
Rappaport do the introductions so that
our white audience
so that our white audience can feel like
more in tune and then I had this one
exact [ __ ] in me this one exec was like
yeah you know we just want to make sure
we're not doing a show just for black
people why not why not it was wild they
don't know by now that nobody enjoys
that more than wise they love everything
about us listen I had a conversation
um with my OG triple OG in this [ __ ]
right and um he was like Champion for me
for me to get a job or whatever and he
said you know Mona is some people that
come from where we come from and look
like how we look and
and they have
um I don't know how you say escaped it
or I don't know try them through it or
whatever but they're educated they're
well spoken you wouldn't know by
speaking to them where they're from you
know they don't wear it on their sleeve
I guess
um to me you're like whitewashing water
down but I don't that's no shade to you
because like I said family I come from
my mother is extremely well spoken my so
are my aunts but they're not watered
down they still are them they're from
North Philly right but those people they
are scared of me what I am or what I
represent
um it's almost like like you're in this
little box and it's like they look
inside of it wow I love it but nobody
else can't see me looking at this like
this is my hidden pleasure like this is
oh this is two wow it's too ghetto it's
too much and those people kind of
gatekeeping those who they keep [ __ ]
like me out and I didn't realize how how
much that [ __ ] happens until kind of
recently and the part that confused me
the most is because if anybody enjoys
don't call me white girl so why girl
like they love this [ __ ] like they eat
it up
you know with my loud round Rowdy ghetto
ass they like it yeah it's the same it's
the same like it's the same thing with
me being like so loudly pro-black right
like
the white girls are loving the loudly
they're like oh my God you might be a
strong black woman
yes yeah at the end of the day
authenticity
always trumps everything yes right and I
feel like
a lot of folks can't recognize what
authenticity is because they are
inauthentic right and so a lot of people
scary and a lot of people in this
business that's the thing they're
they're inauthentic they're very scary
so I've I've had to really this last
year and a half has been a really
um
just kind of an eye-opening year for me
two years for me and and realizing like
where I want the next phase of my life
as an artist to go and understanding
that I need to be independent and
understanding that my energy should
never be about trying to
appeal to or get the attention of these
machines it really should be about the
fans and for a long time I had it
twisted
because they you know this the the
industry makes you feel like what you
need to be doing is attracting the
industry and that's not actually it [ __ ]
no you want the streets listen because
the industry is trying to get to the
streets Perry and that's the thing that
to me is so stupid it's like even when
you get into numbers because people are
so big on following how many people
follow Jack before it's like that [ __ ]
don't mean nothing the the true
influencer the true [ __ ] that
can shake the room I went viral last
year with um something where I'm saying
why you why you being weird to me that
[ __ ]
started to be a pickup line like that
was like an icebreaker you know you'd
throw that in or whatever we my friend
of mine was in L.A and she's eating
pizza and the salt and pepper shakers
say mung mung right from this girl all
the way on the other side from
Philadelphia with some straight back
sitting in the missing side too I think
the reason why things are working for me
now because this happened kind of late
in life and I never knew I wanted to do
this or I could do this is because me
being on the timeline without a BBL with
a missing tooth in my wig off three
lashes on 11 on the other side but being
totally free to say what I gotta say
right talking my [ __ ] maybe talking
about you and your lashes right you come
back I'm on I'm taking it boom I'm from
Philly we call it bidding people say
roasting yo we've raped my grandmother
would bid on me seven in the morning
look at your crusty ass you had to know
how to do this you know it made my skin
thicker and it gave me a certain type of
you know boom but I think it was
refreshing to women that see the same
body in the same building the same hair
and the same eyes you know all the time
it was like damn I want to be like that
too I want to be able to make a video on
my Bonnet because there's so many women
that was like a statement whole time I
just got some [ __ ] to say I'm not about
to get my hair done and forget because I
got 80d literally
why I end up in my Bonnet on a video I'm
not like I learned early on like I'm not
about to sit here and get right you're
gonna [ __ ] the flow up girl I got the
thought happening right now I gotta give
it to you how it is doobie wrap on
um so you would say that you because we
were talking a little earlier and I want
to keep talking about it you you're not
from the ghetto La Ghetto no do you feel
like and you really do feel like people
feel like you can't have certain
statements you can't say certain things
or you don't know what's going on
because you're not from the ghetto and
not only are you not from the ghetto you
smart [ __ ] smart ass not from the
ghetto ass [ __ ]
I mean yeah I think that's
that's definitely a sentiment for some
people
um
you know I think for what it's worth
like it comes from this idea that if you
haven't experienced something then you
shouldn't speak to it in any type of way
and I don't think that is
completely fair you know like I'll have
people say things like you shouldn't
ever speak about you know kids because
you don't have a kid and I'm like okay
but like a lot of y'all's kids teachers
don't have kids like is their opinion
not right valid like I think we have to
move past those type of things and
identify people as the individuals they
are I have a lot of common [ __ ] sense
you can see that but that's the thing
now listen I'm coming from I am a street
[ __ ] I'm not listen wear it cool with
it fell in the whole thing right
um but I don't come from that
necessarily I come from two different
sides my father did 10 years in prison
um a lot of my people on my father's
side went to jail in and out or whatever
and my mother they were all educated
women and my mother didn't break laws
because she don't like the police like I
don't want to talk to them therefore I'm
not doing anything to make me have to
interact with these people I think I had
a full a good like of both I remember
when the recession came
um in 2008 like I said my mother been a
nurse her whole life she was on her
third house at the time it was her
largest like cash investment she had
sold a house prior to that and made 99
000 took that money and bought the next
house for 300 000 and lost everything
um did share and the thing about the
recession that was so crazy was that
everybody was going through the same
thing at the same time and there were no
um it wasn't it wasn't any compassionate
sympathy it wasn't a program right so
it's like they didn't look at it first
like my mother that has worked since
probably 13 or 14. paid taxes since 18
right literally the American dream which
you're supposed to do to get the right
picket fence bootstraps grab them pulled
them shits up worked her whole [ __ ]
life did everything the way she was
supposed to she even married her
raggedy-ass baby daddy you know did the
whole thing right
for
people at the top to [ __ ] that paper up
that's what he's saying the street you
[ __ ] that paper up you [ __ ] that whole
thing up for them to be the ones to [ __ ]
it up and us to suffer at the bottom the
most and a person like her my mother
looked at me and said I understand why
you break the law you and your friends
like like writing and there it clicked
to her why we lived on the other side of
life
um it's a certain respect for a law for
the law that people in the street don't
have you grow up and you see the people
that are supposed to be doing the right
things doing the wrong things you kind
of lose that feeling of okay this person
can save me this person is here to help
me
um it I've always looked at the law like
you know it's just a thing you know it's
a thing it's a hustle you know it's a
way that but I never it never Choice it
and it never morphed into me I know
people that will morph the law into God
and you know they're taking Commandments
and you shouldn't steal I for a long
time that's what I did for a living no
you shouldn't steal from certain folks
maybe but a corporation who's gonna
write that thing off I remember reading
an article in um some type of financial
magazine where uh Walmart did better
they did better with the insurance money
they got from shoplifting almost for
that one year they wouldn't even have
survived it if they didn't have so much
insurance money from [ __ ] that are being
stolen whether it's being stolen or not
people I guess it's weird to me to
conflict it's weird to me to conflate
the Ten Commandments with laws
because you've seen it though right I
have it's just
because it it's just a Kool-Aid Amanda
it just don't make sense like the it
doesn't make sense like the laws are not
written to protect the people in the way
that people think that they are the laws
are meant to protect property if laws
were written to protect people then when
someone like tells you I'm gonna kill
you there would be some level of like
real repercussion for that and there
isn't like people tell you they're gonna
kill you and they're like okay so write
out this piece of fill out this piece of
paper [ __ ] told me he's gonna kill me
this morning like Twitter there you go I
definitely have had that happen on the
Instagrams several times and they're
like well they didn't say anything else
about anybody else so you know what what
can we do but I think um
you know this is what I this is what I
was getting to for me my experience the
SMART Girls the smart people that are
educated necessarily getting in trouble
maybe from the suburbs or whatever it
was a lack of common sense that's what
I'll say I think that's the difference
oh yeah I feel like the girl that is the
street smart right but the book smart
girl with common sense you could come to
the dice game baby you're welcome you
know yeah because you got good sense
it's the lack of Common Sense a lot of
time in New York
I spent a lot of time I [ __ ] I [ __ ]
a couple [ __ ] that played dice games I
mean I learned how to play CeeLo during
Hurricane Sandy because we were stuck in
the house
and I learned how to make well he called
it Chichi which is basically a
well tell me if it's shut up
he was a Feeling Again
um did you do cheese curls with those
noodles and sausage summer sausage
correct yes it's a delicacy love I
understand and you know they sell that
here in bodegas I kid you not eight
dollars you can get a teacher you can
nobody would you need to see that I
don't know that's a that's just like
life experience yeah right like I think
a lot of people don't have common sense
only because they just haven't had life
experience and I mean that on both ends
of the spectrum like even if you have
Street smarts there's still a certain
lack of common sense that a lot of
[ __ ] have simply because
there's uh like there's a narrowed idea
of what is there for you and what makes
sense to actually like be a part of your
Wellness I said this on my Instagram the
other day and
I need to say it here because
it was life-changing for me when my
therapist was like
and this is a she applied it to my ex
but it's really something for everybody
and she was like the difference between
your ex and the person that you are with
now is that the person you're with now
makes decisions to make their life
better your ex makes decisions to make
himself feel better
and like when you look at that and you
apply it to yourself right it helps you
really kind of
check yourself like am I doing like the
common sense thing right or am I just
doing the thing thing right and if
you're just doing the make myself feel
better you're just acting off of like
whatever feelings you have in your body
that are nine times out of ten informed
by whatever experiences you've had and
if you've had a limited amount of
experiences
right right then you don't really have
the sense to that that's why travel is
so important that's why being around
people that people being around people
that ain't your that ain't where you
from like I can honestly tell you I
spent so much time in hip-hop in New
York around people that were completely
different than what I grew up around in
Orlando and it gave me perspective right
it didn't mean that it changed me like
oh I'm trying to be like y'all you know
I'm saying but it just gave me
perspective and I think a lot of those
girls are way different from what you're
what you grew up around you don't think
I wasn't but I think I was born on East
Coast yeah I think I came out the womb
like y'all [ __ ] like that's how I yeah
came into the world and then I had to
find my way to my tribe and I was like
oh [ __ ] y'all [ __ ] you know we know
we're just together when you said
earlier about us bringing together I do
think that black people we are forced to
be reckoned we're together I think that
there's a huge gap with black people and
gay people I think I need that to happen
um more I think we need to get a little
I just think that we will be really I I
love my people a lot Amanda
can fight so I don't even understand how
you building an army and leaving out a
whole Squadron of folks who are like
tough ass [ __ ] listen yeah yeah if You
Buck like what's that yeah but I also
just feel like at the end of the day you
know that's some I don't know homophobia
is weird to me because that's to me too
because I feel like in essence but this
is the big thing for this but this is
the big thing I always looked at it like
and I would say this all the time
because I really didn't understand it
like how can a black person be
homophobic when it's in essence the same
thing somebody hating you for something
that you can't control but the big issue
is is that there's a big amount of black
people old young in between that feel
like that it's a choice and that's where
it's it goes even if it was a choice so
what be because if my point isn't the
same so if my point is how can you as a
black person right and we know about our
history here we know about being
discriminated against people hate us for
no other reason than being how can you
hate a gay person when it's the exact
same thing they're [ __ ] gay they have
no choice in it but there's a group of
people that feel like they do have a
choice even if they did have a choice
why do you care it's not hurting you
like [ __ ] have choices all day long
that Nick like literally like
cisgendered heterosexual people make
choices all day long that hurt other
black people I'm cisgender head females
yes treat with cheese on it I just like
I just think at the end of the day
if people are making choices that don't
affect your life why the [ __ ] do you
care why do you have time why do you
care how somebody else has come coming I
don't I literally and if you sh if you
are a straight person it's like there's
more for you like what I just I don't I
aspire to be a logic this is the logic
you aspire to be lesbian but let me get
people think I'm a lesbian because I
have bass in my voice me too Amanda and
this is the thing
and I don't want to be a lesbian I want
to be I say zyke with love straight
backs I would wear my strap on all day
in jail the stud mm-hmm
they wrench it not only do they run [ __ ]
they're wear their dicks at the
microwave you're allowed to have the
dicks in the jail
oh I don't know um it's against the
rules adobo so where do you get the dick
from is that something that someone puts
in your commissary take your white Go-Go
boot pump your break and let me break it
down to you love you take pencils rubber
band them okay then you take maxi pads
rubber band them okay you might do some
stuffing that you stole out of their
mattress because the mattress is flat as
this is a bit of stuffing in it put that
there a bunch of rubber gloves over
right
there you have a nice good dildo to get
jazzed with you ready Innovation listen
I watched a [ __ ] make a tampon I took
two paper clips and a [ __ ] battery
and little goddamn joint
you're you're you're you're as a chemist
your aunt was a chemist [ __ ] me
that's what I'm saying it comes down the
family line
um either way
those those zykes would wear their strap
at the microwave because clearly How You
Gonna know I got this big ass dick if
I'm not grabbing it by the mic everybody
at the microwave because you ought to
make your Chi feel me now I'm grabbing
this yo you want to spit this TT with me
let me hit you with this strap boom now
we in love [ __ ] fast and you got a
[ __ ] watching your clothes and waxing
the flow but is she protected because
she's doing that
um in jail let me tell you in female
jail the the majority I say like 85
percent of the beef if you're not in a
area that's ran by gangs 85 percent of
the beef is over just lovers just it's
just love her quarrels yeah for the most
part people just madly in love with each
other beefing over she cheating on her
she's not she you know she's not getting
her attention blah blah blah you got
that then you got the gamblers and then
of course the gang bangers but for the
most part the beef is over [ __ ] can
you be in there and not be in any of
those when I was in jail I um I'm Muslim
by faith so I did a lot of praying
I told people how to pray you know and I
told a lot of jokes I used to do a
really good
um Tina impression out big left a good
job in the city at the top of the tears
the whole lower tier would watch and uh
we love a performer on any stage oh my
God that's so how I knew prison that I
could do stand up
um yeah but no it you know Joe I hate
people hate when I say but Joe it ain't
bad there's no bills there's no bills
you get chicken on Fridays you know what
I mean I think maybe you were in a
particular jail that wasn't bad because
Alabama jails was a doozy yikes it's
just about it's just about you and you
know like I'm laughing at a funeral I've
always taken my harder times and made
them better times and it's like I don't
think I would do well in jail I'm a bit
of a social butterfly I think you would
get into a lot of debates and I think
you were getting a fight first week I
think that you don't understand that I
am not getting in a fight
have you ever gotten a physical fight in
your life I have only been in one
physical fight in my life and I won
but I'm fine I fought a [ __ ] three
weeks ago I haven't really grew from
that just yet and let me tell you
something I've been threatened to be
fought several times and it didn't and
it didn't happen because to call your
cousin because I was I I would like to
call your cousin
so why we fight Amanda because we're
[ __ ] Americans I
I think it's like Oh Black no
good old Americans we like to get [ __ ]
up we like to kill [ __ ] and take [ __ ]
[ __ ] I'm a [ __ ] American okay I feel
you but I'm 100 full bloody baby we have
to like Park this [ __ ]
rage I have a lot of race you might end
up in prison for murder because you take
her ears and bang her [ __ ]
boom homicide I will I've punched a
window out
get you you're sexy I like like I've
literally like but like so you know I my
daughter's never been a fighting she's
so mortified by it I'm like I mean you
don't have to fight people it's not I
listen I mean people are adults they say
they're never in a fight and I'm like oh
my God how but it's because it's just
because of where you from or were you
raised in the type of situation and
maybe even your um temperament or
whatever I had to fight I didn't have to
I didn't have any siblings I am pale as
[ __ ] I'm from North Philly and now yeah
I remember my mom being like look you
had to fight them [ __ ] and close the
door like what you gonna do you can't
keep coming in here you know talking
[ __ ] you know what I mean or coming here
crying to me I can remember fighting
right and the girl's mother like me
finally getting my heart up to do
something the girl's mother getting
involved and then me coming to tell my
mother and my mother's like all right
and she's getting dressed getting ready
for the fight in the middle I call my
grandmother and I tell her the story
when me and my mother are walking
outside my mother has full sweatsuit on
she is so serious we're walking towards
and it's so crazy listen this is
hilarious I talk to my mom now about it
I remember saying mom I was so scared
and you were so relaxed she was like Hey
at the moment I took a volume that day I
never took a volume before and I took
one to sleep that's why I was like whoa
it's a rough day for this but let's get
it going but as we're walking out Amanda
this is a memory etched in my head from
eight years old as we're walking to this
lady's house remind to confront this
lady my grandmother pulls up in a Toyota
Camry
she parks in one move
not double back not looking nothing she
gets out with a small stick she skips
the lady say oh you gonna hit me Bessie
you won't let me Bessie my grandma over
hands what would the bamboo stick they
get up throw hands my grandmother whoops
this [ __ ] ass I'm talking I mean right
left all in my my mother my grandmother
learned how to fight and Joe Frazier's
oh wow boxing
um you know Philadelphia my grandmother
knows how to fight I'm too jammed up low
uppercut to the body whooping this [ __ ]
ass I'm screaming get off my grandma's
so tremended get off my girl my mother
elbows me your grandmother's on her shut
up yeah and my grandma is whooping her
[ __ ] ass and then fast forward we're
on our porch and it's a sea of people
because that lady was more popular than
us my mother was quiet she all she did
was work or whatever and it's a city
when they yelling why y'all do that
though why y'all do that there and my
mom's like she fought my mind one-on-one
and the whole crowd was like damn
damn
it's getting bigger and bigger bigger
bigger but when you grow up like that
you have a different you know and I
purposely by Design put my children in
the suburbs so it's like no I don't you
don't have to fight you don't in the way
my daughter feels about it it's so like
Mommy I want to beat somebody up you
know cause when girls come at her like
that a girl the other day in school said
to her did you say such and such because
if you did I was gonna crack you and
when she told me the story I said oh
[ __ ] what you say back and she says I
told her crack me for what I didn't even
do that that's me and your dog me and
your daughter are the same
me and your daughter the same
my daughter five eight and she's a
[ __ ] punk that's what I said
I don't want her to fight but at the
same time but here's what I'm saying I
if you said that I was going to crack
you the way I was raised that's a
[ __ ] threat cracker that's just how I
came up you have a visible square around
you that's my mother didn't raise me if
they come in the Square sock this [ __ ]
before she get you first that's just you
know when I think about it it's like yo
they raised a psycho and of course I end
up in prison although
is fear you just want your kid to be
able to protect themselves and make it
back home while you're doing your double
you know you have to have also though
the cognition to know when
uh he keeps telling us the time man but
we ain't stopping somebody stand up
double time it's like Amanda seals I'm
really excited everybody here sweating
and sleep we going we can do this All
Night
I just don't I think you got to choose
what do they say choose your battles
that's not a battle to me we're choosing
I mean it was like why am I fighting
over something I didn't even say that
I'm not gonna go I'm not going down for
that now if you if I did say this [ __ ]
and you want to fight well you know what
let's hop to it yeah did you see the
tick tock challenge that went by her
when I hated it so bad um somebody came
to fight Mommy and they're bringing
their son yeah listen so I said it to my
son you know my son said he's bringing
the summer I'm like yeah he said call
the police two of them since it's two of
them
I love smoosh he loves classical music
his favorite movie is the Titanic he
hates rap I love my signs and Capricorn
is an [ __ ] but I love him because
he's so himself you know what I mean
he's not a devotional [ __ ] clone real
quick because we have to go will I ever
find love because I'm on it and all the
time talking [ __ ] how honest with
yourself are you
[Music]
then no
what do you mean honest with yourself
what are you talking about
about what and meaning what regarding
what regarding it like what you trying
to say I'm trying to say how honest with
you are you how honest with you how
honest with yourself are you about your
own toxicity you think you better than
me Amanda I think I trick question
no I do know I know mine because I
because let me tell you that this love
[ __ ] is a very humbling experience am I
right Trey
it is a very humbling experience and you
got to choose every day
to go the route
and I feel like a lot of us strong
people I'm not going to make it just
about women a lot of us strong because
it's not a gender thing when it comes to
the reality that our strength oftentimes
informs an ego that does not serve us
people like strong men [ __ ]
know what I'm trying to say is that what
they what we are considering to be
strong is actually some fake weak [ __ ]
yeah it's a facade it's a facade like
there's confidence there's arrogance
confidence is on is based on real [ __ ]
arrogance some fake [ __ ] and I think a
lot of us are first of all a lot of us
have never experienced real love
okay so we don't even know how to
recognize it when it's happening
and then a lot of us really truly are
not honest with ourselves we are not we
will tell ourselves that like we
identify these flaws about ourselves and
we accept these flaws well guess what
like great good for [ __ ] you that you
accepted the flaws are you gonna do
anything about that or what because the
accepting thing I'm gonna tell you an
epiphany I had the other day
so you know you get into this
relationship
and it's finally like
healthy in the sense that both parties
want the best for each other right so
that's the healthy part
now do both parties have the tools
that's its own that's its own process
but there's at least the foundation of
like we want the best for ourselves
individually and we want the best for
ourselves together so that's that right
but then
you think I found this person that I can
be my complete self with I can be my
whole self with
and that's a beautiful thing but baby
not all parts of you are good not all
parts of you are Advanced not all parts
of you are healthy
so what happens sometimes is you get
over comfortable in the we're showing
our whole self [ __ ] and you start
letting them shits out you start letting
that toxicity out and you kind of like
make it like you you trick yourself into
thinking that the it's healthy that I
get to be all parts of myself in this
relationship and the person stays with
me but really that's some [ __ ] up
thinking because your toxicity ain't
good for you and it ain't good for him
and it ain't good for or for whoever
you're with and it ain't good for the
scenario and it's only your
responsibility to check that [ __ ] and I
think a lot of us don't really
allow ourselves
to be honest with ourselves enough to
say I'm not checking my toxicity and I'm
thinking that the healthy part of this
relationship is me getting to be toxic
and still be loved and the only person
who's going to Unconditionally Love You
is your mother there should be no
expectation for someone else to
Unconditionally Love You in that way
love has conditions you know and it's
not like
you know you gained weight or you had a
health issue or that's different but
when we choose to let these dark parts
of ourselves find their way into
something that's supposed to be light we
are being irresponsible and I think a
lot of us don't hold ourselves
accountable for that in these
relationships and I know for a fact that
I have not done that and I've had to
like
really get real with myself that that's
something that I need to like
bone up on yeah realizing that like
wanting a good man or wanting a good
situation and you might not be well like
ready for that like I have I came up in
a time where if you didn't have a
boyfriend or you didn't have a [ __ ] if
something was wrong with you 2022
what time was that because because that
because that I'm still getting DMS that
say you a bitter [ __ ] don't nobody want
you yeah you a single bitter [ __ ] and
I'm like look at me am I a man of my dog
like because I still feel compelled to
have to say like we'll see this
this is me yeah when really it's like
[ __ ] you right right but I I feel like
the younger girls and shout out to you
young [ __ ] that y'all do a really good
job of like being single and glowing and
working on you and getting healthy yeah
caring about yourself and making sure
you love yourself first I didn't come up
in a time like that I know you had the
[ __ ] you had to get the [ __ ] you
paraded him around and you didn't parade
around you purposely made sure his
[ __ ] head was in the background of
the picture to let these [ __ ] know I
don't need a [ __ ] cause I got a [ __ ]
even if you had a completely empty
relationship I was in a relationship for
seven or eight years nothing we didn't
even [ __ ] but we did all appearances we
did everything wow you know what I mean
we did it what was he getting out of
that
I think
dare I say it I think that he wanted to
be married to a light-skinned girl I
think he wanted
um I think he wanted light-skinned
children I think he wanted a girl with a
fat ass
and I think he want I think that he
liked the coolness of me like I think
that he thought that I was cool and I
think that he was attracted by the the
really negative Street side of me you
know what I mean I think I think that I
was like his past to finally be a thug a
little bit where'd you find this guy we
met in height he sounds like a c-band
and then we years later we reunited
because we had like a crush on each
other in school but you do understand
now that he's a cornball ass [ __ ] [ __ ]
he's a Virgo like I would rather eat a
doo-doo stew because first I said I eat
a sand sandwich I like a Virgo a Virgo
man cancer Virgos are well I don't know
a lot of Virgo man but cancer Virgo is
supposed to be like very Phelps hates
that we talk about look at Phelps he's
dying he hates the sign conversation he
doesn't believe in it even though he's
the most tourist tourist I've ever met
he's a completely part of him hating it
though like Taurus exactly so [ __ ]
awesome Brand This is my plan once I get
like rich rich me and Phelps are [ __ ] on
a bed of a hundred thousand dollars and
then we'll be together forever how do
you feel about that
I love you we'll see I will say that
does sound very unsanitary yeah yeah
because the money is very dirty so corny
is stopping it's I'm just it's I don't
want you to get a yeast infection from
the dollars
so you can hear me in your head and
you're gonna be like she [ __ ] it up
for me damn have you done shrooms yet I
don't do drugs um
did you enjoy yourself a lot here I did
I would have liked us to have some more
jovial conversations because I feel like
we were very serious and you're like a
[ __ ] joke to you Amanda no but you
have good jokes I am a joke I love to
joke people always have the serious
conversations with me like Gillian then
wouldn't even let me on a podcast
because they were like you're too
serious
there's so many things I could say about
that but I will try I love who I love
um you know I started that's why my
first I did podcasting and like two
months later I was on that podcast which
was like at the time the biggest music
podcast in the country I sat between two
bald head [ __ ] debating and and
arguing about stuff like I remember me
and Gilly had a debate about
um stay-at-home moms because I think he
said and I quote or lazy [ __ ] and
being a Salesman doesn't count as a job
because you have to take care of your
[ __ ] kids because that's your duty
from God and the least you could do is
get a [ __ ] job you lazy [ __ ] bum
um well listen we have a a a uh uh I
have so many more questions we don't
have time invite me on your show so we
can talk more can we do one more
question that I don't have to be so
serious yeah okay I'm ready
um
I'm just a very intense person let me
think
um
let me think okay because we did have a
conversation about dating thugs like
dating Street [ __ ] or whatever tell me
your most memorable situation with
dating the street guy
funny is crazy as wild as night or
whatever
talking about naive Amanda like your
first Thug [ __ ]
um being in a car and I
pressed a button thinking I was turning
down the radio and I was actually
opening a stash box
still in it it was it was actually empty
and I was like is this it's for I was
like is this an ashtray I think your
radio's broken he was like don't touch
it yeah
um yeah I mean I think I actually
you know have listened I've listened to
a lot of rap yeah I've listened to a lot
of rap so I've actually been more savvy
than I thought I remember at one time
yeah like I remember at one point in
time talking to a dude and he was like
yeah I'm about to go over here and do
this thing
and we were on the phone and he was like
oh wait I just a policeman just pulled
up
and I was like they're about to raid
wherever you're going and he was like no
I don't think so and I was like pretty
sure that's what's about to happen
um it feels like a lock set a locks
record that I've heard and that's
hilarious Amanda guess what they got
rated and he would have been under the
jail wow you saved that [ __ ] my little
Suburban where non-shrooms Captain Save
A [ __ ] Captain well baby I should have
a whole NAACP award dedicated to me for
them such a good conversation before the
show started but y'all can't get none of
that no but people think I hate black
men like that's like a real like
narrative on the internet
um they love to say it they love it they
come at me they're like Amanda seals
hates black magic
black man I'm like I
I don't know why I've never dated
outside my race I really am interested
in I used to the guy you described
earlier today used to be my dream man a
man that had lived a certain type of
Life maybe even went to jail did some
jail time got out of jail became his own
business you know a self uh entrepreneur
got some successes in that by taking all
of the things that he learned on the
street and applying them to you know
you're still young right legal I guess
the thing about it is is that street
people right let's just say a drug
dealer okay you are doing your own
advertising you're doing your own you're
you're doing stuff yeah you're on
security yes right I mean it's it's a
lot so you can kind of take those skills
and move them to something different I
definitely wrong some Street ethics to
this internet [ __ ] I used to say because
it was kind of crazy I went from
obscurity to now I'm sitting with famous
people I'm working with famous people
I'm doing this I'm doing that and you
know he would say are you scared of the
industry because there is a lot of
people that don't have any types of
Industry that believe in the illuminati
people really think that you sell your
soul okay
listen and I said to them I'm like look
I will give you my baby father I keep
offering them they won't take them
because and it's so saturated last
Illuminati guy that did me he left me on
scene I'm such a loser that is so [ __ ]
up either way um but that used to be
like my dream guy you know what I mean
like that but now I don't I dream of
having the kind of guy that doesn't know
anything about where I'm from and I
don't know anything about where he's
from and then we learn each other and
then we fall in love and then we run off
to the sunset all he has to do is eat my
butt Dre other than that there's no like
I don't want nobody
I can't I don't know how y'all do it
wrap this up this is gonna this [ __ ]
going crazy now what are you talking
about talking about I just I'm not her
mic I'm not in the booty eating game but
and I'm not getting your butt no so you
never let the ass and if you found your
drink okay your man right now shout out
to him shout out to him he's amazing
we've talked about him for so long today
um
him right
everything's going great he's perfect
y'all about to get married he says look
babe I've been trying I've been thinking
about doing something wild could you
lick my ass you're not no yeah you're a
little kid so
um
what is it about the booty eat listen I
game into the world first of all I've
always had a big ass so having a big
butt always a guy like bite your butt
cheek or kiss your butt it's always like
a thing or whatever but the first time I
got my S8 the whole thing was like okay
you eat my ass it's like an eagle thing
he's eating my ass but now it's a
requirement in fact if you don't eat
this ass you can't get none of this
[ __ ]
[ __ ] listen we all have our one
yeah but you have tried it and you don't
like it I have had
um
thank you
I have had a there there has been an ass
eat that started to take place okay
you buy a Philly [ __ ] actually and uh I
think it's gonna eat your ass they're
gonna buy you a cheese steak they're
gonna eat your hands this is all right I
and for the sake and for the sake of
experience I was like okay you know
let's let's just see how this take your
brain out of you thinking too much about
it I just didn't lie well yeah but
because [ __ ] comes out of it so I am
thinking about [ __ ] comes out of there a
real team player right after each ass
you gonna give them a good that's what
you're gonna do
that is so like you said nothing better
makes your [ __ ] wet and it literally
makes my [ __ ] like constricted like
runs away it's like like it went it
enveloped on itself because you need to
grow up huh well I'm an old [ __ ] you
are so mature this conversation is it's
gotten to the tubes I thought I liked
you
um I'm so uncomfortable with the idea of
it you're exactly in the position of
getting your ass licked perfectly it's
the diaper change position I just don't
um wow so look this I don't want to get
too much in your business bowling ball
do you like a bowling ball I don't know
what okay when you have a when you have
a bowling ball you got that Thumb in the
ball you yeah I'm not I don't want
nothing going on with my ass I mean and
maybe part of it is because
it's not going right what is she talking
about I think it's because you said you
bit you have a you said you have a fat
ass and I have a proportional Adder it
doesn't matter listen there's I've
experienced the bowling ball and it
wasn't a strike damn
no also like what no dicks are big
I don't I prefer smaller penises
interesting I'm somebody that if I meet
a guy I ask for dick pics I'm big on
that in fact the guy that gave me pcsd
I'm like yo let me see your dick because
he was so tall but how what big how were
his hands what was the size of his hands
were pretty sizy too and like most tall
guys or whatever because I've I've had a
tornado with small hands and let me tell
you it was interesting how the
proportions add up if European is is
bigger than like eight inches seven and
a half I'm not [ __ ] comfortable
you're gonna rearrange Furniture yeah I
don't I prefer an average size penis
which is six inches five inches I'm fine
I'm a girth girl if you're very short
but you're stocky we good okay you know
what I mean I mean there's it's a whole
experience I mean I've experienced the
parking a hot dog in the hallway
situation yes and that's just it makes
you question yourself yes because you're
like am I you know what I mean
out here at the cavern what yeah no I've
been know what's rough about that is
like every sexual position you get into
the dick keep sliding out and then
you're blaming yeah yeah you're blaming
you know what I didn't realize for a
long time what I okay
I didn't know I was supposed to be
faking the orgasm
I did not know that like legit okay so
let me just say so what do you just sit
there quietly
I mean no
but you have to fake the finish so we
can wrap it up I did not know that
so like I didn't understand that [ __ ]
was mad
because I wasn't
achieving this climax I did not know
that and then the this one [ __ ] I dated
was like
[Music]
I hate to spit like why because I was
having a good time yeah are you hitting
the walls I was having a good time and
he was like you just never finish and I
was like but you finished yeah and he
was like yeah but you're not you're not
signaling the accomplishment ramp it up
but I literally had no idea like no one
taught me this he was like you're not
signaling the accomplishment and it just
makes me feel like I'm not doing what
I'm supposed to be doing and I'm like
but I'm
why aren't I having the final right and
it wasn't until
I had a dude who really
um you know how do I put this he was
broke and so his and so I think that in
his mind he was like I can't give
financially so I'm gonna give vaginally
ain't nobody gonna [ __ ] you like a [ __ ]
need a place to stay [ __ ] and but he
like unlocked
the the children it was like he saw he
solved The Da Vinci Code yeah and then I
was like oh I can I can do this but I
really did not know the Bleaker the
future the better that dick is I had a
[ __ ] get up out of me before
and just like in the mid like
and like he just got up and was like I
mean you ain't gonna come anyway so
what's the point and like he like
y'all know who you y'all know him too
and he uh and he just like went in the
next like he like went across the hall
and like went and played video games
with his homeboy and I was just laying
there like a trout you don't know how
many I don't think I don't think men and
I have conversations with my boys all
the time I don't think men understand
how many women they just don't come but
we also didn't know our bodies like
first of all it is not you ever squirted
on a [ __ ] and he acted like he was
drowning I've squirted twice and I'm
still not convinced about it like it's
just a weird thing the guy I squirted
with couldn't really [ __ ] so it was very
strange and I squirted with him it's
only happen with him but I did see it
he's seeing solid so I know it happened
but I'm still very like I tussled with
the squirt things the first time I
squirted with somebody he literally was
like
and it was it was PTSD yeah I don't know
listen all right that's again that's why
the lesbians look really happy don't
[ __ ] coming I'm going I'm coming but
they're doing anatomy I'm coming Brenda
anatomy class I'm coming they have a
special understanding of all the holes
and the intricacies of things so but you
ever see two [ __ ] scissors
it ain't no way that's not fun it ain't
no way that's not fun I'm with that [ __ ]
listen
um we have to wrap it up yes Dre said
and I quote I wish you Richard shut the
[ __ ] up she texted
um we have a second on the podcast
called the dark side of the DM yep would
you like to share a DM or do you want me
to share mine share yours all right um I
show Amanda mine already and this is
dated this is Monday 8 55 in the morning
greetings I'm a member of the great
Illuminati then there is three upside
down red triangles because that's the
secret yeah yeah
um you want to you want to know the
light dot dot first of all money is not
a problem for us come to us today and
get rid of wealth Fame power and
knowledge it says get rid of I think
they meant that backwards
um first membership benefits of
five hundred thousand dollars USD if
interested reply yes
um and then I said please take blank
first and then
Chuck here do you want to read I really
did that's what I said and they left me
on scene membership benefits yeah so I
mean do you get is there a point system
one more
um listen
um
so I got a big problem I'm single and
first things first I'm young and I'm
doing me I [ __ ] with this dude I really
like him because he's everything I want
in a man because our lifestyles we
aren't really in a relationship because
of our lifestyles we're only in
relationships that's some [ __ ] that he
told her yeah she bought it yeah you
definitely bought that like a so far
baby with me working in the ticket booth
down here I can't possibly you know
settle down because you never know
you know and doing nightlife
okay so I met this dude he's fine and we
fine and we kicking he tell me that
um him and old dude got major beef and
do I know him I told him I do know him
and eventually I told him I was [ __ ]
with dudes so basically she meets this
guy's op okay but they're not a
relationship but they like each other
whatever okay he was upset at first but
now I feel bad because the other guy is
still a little bit in the picture I
don't know how to shake this guy we're
all in our 20s so we definitely have
time to figure things out but I don't
know what to do I honestly like both of
them but I might like the main do more
he doesn't know anything but if he finds
out he's going to tell a boy we
definitely still in tune lol this [ __ ]
is real it's not that real it's like not
a big deal they're both losers just move
on you know what a [ __ ] told me one
time when I was having one of these like
you know all I don't know what to do he
was like he not special he is right and
it's like crazy [ __ ] in a couple years
he will be a faint memory like all the
[ __ ] yeah
[Music]
how good he ate my ass
I don't have those memories but um it's
in my journal I feel you listen one more
last one okay Mona I love you I just
need advice my dad has been an alcoholic
my whole life I was raised by his mother
him and my mother both were in and out
of my life in 2013 my mom passed I'm 32
my dad is in his late 50s since age 45
my dad has went back to school changed
his whole life around stopped drinking
and now he's making close to 80 to 90k
per year it gives me such I don't know
oh no the question he gives me such a
hard time whenever I need him for
financial help and my wrongful feeling
like he should make sure I'm good for
the time that he wasn't there or has the
money both sell since I'm grown I'm 32
years old
um thank you sorry as long as I provide
a backstory I am grown and I just need
to know for honorary mentioned this is a
man
interesting it's a good job right you
know what I've gotten this a lot just to
let y'all know I've gotten a lot where
people's parents they just found them or
they just met them and and it's so crazy
it's like instantaneously give me money
it's always but I will say the parent is
always in a good Financial what they
consider a good financial situation is
never like oh just give me money it's a
good but I can record give me money to
do what though the [ __ ] off Amanda I um
I I can't this is what I will say my
father never helped my mother my mother
never went for child support just
something that she didn't do
um I remember around like the 1819 that
part where you think you grown but you
really ain't grown you kind of came it's
not a kid but you want to be grown
sometimes I would call him for money I
remember calling because I wanted to go
to Community College and it was like my
mother was paying for it my mother paid
for everything but I wanted him to help
and he was like [ __ ] I [ __ ] you paved
your way through high school I ain't
wasting my money [ __ ] and I'm
like [ __ ] you [ __ ] [ __ ] you and we
arguing and then I told him and I quote
I'll shoot you in the back of your curly
ass head and I hurried up and left
before he got there because he told me
he was gonna punch me in my face I mean
my father had a rocky relationship I
mean my father sophomore year of college
I was like trying to like
like make amends with him or whatever
the [ __ ] and uh my mom had like misread
the
the enrollment like for the registration
thing and it turned out that like I
needed to come up with three thousand
dollars in order to register or else
like like within two days or else I
could not go back to school yeah and I
was on the phone with my mom my I was on
the phone with my dad and I was like you
know this is what's going on and again
we're trying to mend our relationship
and I was like this is what's going on
and he said so what are you gonna do
yeah it's like what are you gonna do and
he and this is a man who went to Harvard
wow this is the man who went to Tufts
this is a man who went to UPenn wow this
is not like somebody who doesn't
understand the value of Education it's
incredibly selfish like oh Next Level
and uh
he ugh what is it Gemini oh he's a
[ __ ] demon he's a demon he's a demon
and so my but you know I say all that to
say that it don't matter where they come
from a narcissist is going to be a
narcissist yeah and you know I think
when you tell when you talk about your
dad me and my dad had similar
interactions just without the same
language but it was the same sentence
[ __ ] yeah but I want to just say this
before Dre stops US yeah [ __ ] that
Stefan Drake I just want to say this I
do think
as black folks part of our really
getting to the core of increasing our
Legacy is also understanding that we do
have to help our kids along and like
these white folks like they really be
they really be doing that and we that's
our goal we'd be like nah [ __ ] my mind
you struggle and I know that there's a
love part to that that says like I want
you to get strong but I will tell you
there is something that's also strength
building in having support right and I
want to see us do that I want to see us
have trusts I want us to see us have
trust funds and people need to
understand that you do not need to be
rich to have a trust there are there are
pro bono agencies that will create trust
for black folks so it's not even about
that but I think when I hear that story
and you say there's so many stories like
that like
a lot of people really do need money
and you I know that there was a time in
my early 30s where I did not have it and
I needed some help to get over to hump
[ __ ] I'm here now but go ahead bull you
just need some help to get over the hump
it's not like I just want it so I can
sit on my [ __ ] ass I need it so I can
have some peace of mind to get to to to
not be [ __ ] scrambling for this money
while I'm trying to figure out how to
create this like life for myself me here
for my peace of mind there you go
um this has been fun listen love you
lots and make sure I come to your show
make sure you come back here yes you are
so smart and you're beautiful and you
look really really young and you're not
six foot like I thought you were five
six but your brain is so big it's just
beautiful I love you I appreciate you
coming and I would like another hug even
though you're not a hugger I appreciate
you knowing I'm not a hugger give me
this
um we also manifest things what do you
manifested for this year for next year
what are you bringing into your life
what are you welcoming into your life
next year
I am welcoming into my life
oh
I'm welcoming into my life
peace
in my relationship in my business
peace and flowing movement I think I've
had a lot of like I'm hitting walls I'm
hitting walls and I don't want it
anymore I really want to just break down
the dams and create a stream of
fortuitousness
I know you'll get everything you want
and more hey Dre you can cut this part
out but
[Music]